Laura Helena Verbinen

(47) 99915-0707 - lauraverbinen@gmail.com - Curitiba, PR LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/laura-helena-verbinen-8b5308211/

GitHub: https://github.com/laura-2

SUMMARY

Dedicated developer with 2 years of experience, holding a degree in Systems Analysis and Development from PUCPR. I possess a strong knowledge of HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. I specialize in projects involving React and Nextjs. However, I am open to learning and exploring new technologies. Currently seeking new opportunities to continue studying and further delve into the world of Front-End.

EDUCATION

Pontifical Catholic University of Paraná, Curitiba, PR Degree: Systems Analysis and Development Technology 03/2021 – 08/2023

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Front-End Developer (Internship) Brasil Foods, Curitiba, PR

09/2022 - 09/2023

- Developed birthday cards using only HTML, CSS, and JavaScript technologies.
- Created an app from scratch for scanning QR codes using JavaScript, React Native, SQLite, and styled components.
- Gained experience in using new work platforms, such as Azure, GIT commands, and Agile methodologies like SCRUM.

Python Programming Language Instructor

Hello Future, Porto Velho, RO 07/2021 - 10/2021

- Taught the Python programming language to students aged 8 to 13.
- Studied and taught platforms like Scratch and Python Turtle.

LANGUAGES

Native Portuguese - Advanced English - Basic Spanish - Intermediate Indonesian

EXTRACURRICULAR COURSES/ SKILLS

- Course: Full stack JavaScript: Create a project with React and Node.js (API with Express) 28 hours
- Course: Practice HTML and CSS in Web Projects (Flexbox and mobile-first) 59 hours
- Course: Framework Angular 56hs
- Course: WordPress 20h
- Course: From Scratch: HTML and CSS for web projects (responsiveness) 48 hours
- Course: HTML and CSS 62 hours
- Mobile (React Native) 18 hours
- Programming (Javascript, HTML, PHP) 62 hours
- Front-end (Javascript, Typescript, React, Next.js, Tailwind CSS, CSS, Bootstrap 4, Styled Components, Material UI, StoryBook) 198 hours
- DevOps (Linux, Git, GitHub) 12 hours